one of my favorite online personalities
I've seen him in person names Kyle sees
I've recommended him to people
constantly because he's like a Tony
Robbins that brings humor to it had just
in the sense of humanity and
authenticity he's part of the reason I
am able to be online and authentic is
because seeing him on stage kind of
without script and just going for it and
he's much better at it
he's a comedian and an entertainer so he
can do that in the moment and maybe I
can't but knowing he's partly the reason
I'm on an authenticity mission starting
with his work about three years ago it's
probably when I when I found out about
him and in 2017 I went to a live event
of his in Los Angeles and at the time
his fiancee was pregnant very pregnant
sitting in the front row and he talks
about her like she is the love of his
life he finally found her they were
finally able to have a baby and it was a
girl and now the daughter is almost
ob3 I guess this this summer and he
talks about them as a monogamous family
unit
he definitely portrays that and this
woman has come forward saying that he's
had a relationship with her for roughly
the last year and then multiple other
women had come forward with the very
similar stories of him getting them to
drink alcohol despite their sobriety I
think a lot of these women have sexual
abuse in their history he they pay to be
at his events and then he you know
professes his love and sleeps with them
whether that story is true or not I can
I can imagine that in the highest order
of that story if it is true is that he
was actually open and honest with all
the women in his life
and including hit the mother of his
child his fiancee that they're in an
open relationship and
he is you know what he says everyone's
just love and he's just loving all these
women and you know that's that's the
world he lives in
but even if he was honest with all of
those women and they knew exactly where
they stand her soul being a spiritual
leader and plying them with alcohol
skeezy and gross but that he wasn't
honest with the rest of us and his brand
is authenticity his brand is yes
everyone loves and everyone's evolving
but that he's doing it in full view and
that he is honest and open about that
journey and this is a huge piece of that
journey so I get it humanity is not
ready for polyamory to be polyamorous
out in the open
costs something but if your brand is
authenticity and you're not open about
that you're choosing profit you're
choosing to have a million dollar
company over your integrity and that is
and yet it makes sense to do that right
how do you have staff how do you have
how do you reach this number of people
if you're out in the open about that
kind of thing I'm not saying he is
polyamorous in any way but like that's
the highest level that I can give him if
this if these stories are in any way
true which based on the fact that it's
authenticity to have been following him
I can't imagine this was one never gonna
come to light because when you preach
authenticity and people have that in
them they're gonna eventually be
authentic like the truth will come out I
could have seen this unfolding it's
something that somewhere along that line
someone has to claim yes
word but even if he's probably amorous
right that like yes we were in a poly
blasian ship his wife knew about it we
all knew about it but I feel little
dupes because there was a shrinking
involved and this misalignment of power
and yet as a society that is very
masculine feminine so that's like a
whole other video element of itself but
when you have a community that's one
branded on authenticity but even more so
when it's around is one leader like Kyle
he's evolving out loud community then
when they fall from grace
especially around their branding right
when it's like oh you're not being
authentic then the community falls apart
much more readily than if there isn't
that that structure what's happening in
my community my physical eat with them
community with this woman this
interactions not gonna make the
community fall apart because it's not
dependent on either her or I be in there
it's not dependent on our relationship
the only way it would make the community
fall apart is if it was pushed under the
rug
kept in secrecy she kept doing that to
other people everyone like there are
things that could fracture it for sure
around this but with authenticity with
openness and transparency and with
people willing to be part of that if she
doesn't want it to be transparent that's
clear because there's power in oh wait I
acted horribly and I don't want anyone
to know so I can still act horribly and
still nobody knows and still act
horribly and still nobody knows keeping
it secret because their shame involved
and shame can break things whereas out
in the open at least you are owning it
like even if you're not by choice this
thing happened or you're dying at and
saying it didn't happen but like there's
something about having a central leader
versus a dispersed interconnected
community where it's not the like leader
in their relationship and their
relationships other people like you know
a pyramid it's more of a molecule more
like this connection and this connection
and Dunbar's number of connections and
that is the resiliency of community so
that is I'm sitting with a lot of of
just I'm not angry not even like a
disappointment but like this awakening
and understanding of like oh this is why
we don't want to sense a leader even
though society wants a central leader
and it's like and then the central
leader can't be authentic and open
because they wouldn't have as much of a
following and couldn't have as much
impact and then it falls apart when they
fall apart
instead of let's do it together let's
interconnect and one person falls part
we pull them together and there is no
such thing as falling down and not
getting back up unless you truly can't
be part of community and are so toxic
that like you refuse to change and just
keep moving okay but then that's if you
keep the fewer toxic and move from
community to community following the
same pattern that's your learning
you got some role there but there's
something here that is just for me to
learn and I will be learning it so the
community the the neighbor who refused
to leave my doorway and had a that was a
whole other conversation I went to
another video on it's like the forced
conversation versus the invited
conversation I'm gonna end this here and
do that video next yeah I don't know
what I'm titling this video
Kyle seasoned inauthenticity and the
vulnerability of community thank you